<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Vault]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Vault</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 08:03:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 08:03:45 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Recent Files]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="03 - School/00 - School MOC" data-href="03 - School/00 - School MOC" href="03-school/00-school-moc.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">00 - School MOC</a><br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="04 - Games/00 - Games MOC" data-href="04 - Games/00 - Games MOC" href="04-games/00-games-moc.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">00 - Games MOC</a><br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="05 - Literature/00 - Literature MOC" data-href="05 - Literature/00 - Literature MOC" href="05-literature/00-literature-moc.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">00 - Literature MOC</a><br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="02 - Coding &amp; Software/00 - Coding MOC" data-href="02 - Coding &amp; Software/00 - Coding MOC" href="02-coding-&amp;-software/00-coding-moc.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">00 - Coding MOC</a><br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="01 - Japanese/00 - Japanese MOC" data-href="01 - Japanese/00 - Japanese MOC" href="01-japanese/00-japanese-moc.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">00 - Japanese MOC</a><br>Side Project:<br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="00 - Index/00 - Vault Remake" data-href="00 - Index/00 - Vault Remake" href="00-index/00-vault-remake.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">00 - Vault Remake</a>]]></description><link>00-index/00-main-page.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Index/00 - MAIN PAGE.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 08:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goal?]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>To remake my vault from the ground up, all information from all similar files consolidated into one central file for that info.<br><br>To make it easier to explore my vault, and to reduce clutter, while also leaving room for growth.<br><br>I will achieve this goal by going over all my past school work, and other information, and sorting it into categories, as so I can move it all into a designated file. This will reduce clutter, while keeping essential information.<br><br>It will depend how well kept I keep this vault.]]></description><link>00-index/00-vault-remake.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Index/00 - Vault Remake.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:22:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How does this work?]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Last page: <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="00 - Index/00 - MAIN PAGE" data-href="00 - Index/00 - MAIN PAGE" href="00-index/00-main-page.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">00 - MAIN PAGE</a><br><br>In this vault, I separate my work into 6 files - Japanese, Coding &amp; Software, School, Games, Literature, and my Daily Notes. Japanese contains notes, school work, and flashcards for Japanese. Coding &amp; Software contains EVERYTHING to do with coding and software that I work on. School contains... school stuff. Games contains everything to do with games I play (but do not make). And, finally, literature contains reviews on books I’ve read, or poems I’ve read.<br><br>It works best for me. If you’re reading this, and it doesn’t work for you, fuck you, work on your own.<br><br>I’d start with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="00 - Index/00 - MAIN PAGE" data-href="00 - Index/00 - MAIN PAGE" href="00-index/00-main-page.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">00 - MAIN PAGE</a> if you want to see the last things I worked on before you either forced your way into my hard drive, or, if you’re me and have amnesia (if you are me, hi).<br>Next page: <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="00 - Index/02 - Why I made this folder" data-href="00 - Index/02 - Why I made this folder" href="00-index/02-why-i-made-this-folder.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">02 - Why I made this folder</a>]]></description><link>00-index/01-how-this-works.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Index/01 - How this works.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:59:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[02 - Why I made this folder]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Last page: <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="00 - Index/01 - How this works" data-href="00 - Index/01 - How this works" href="00-index/01-how-this-works.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">01 - How this works</a><br>Hello, again! Figured I should give some more reasoning behind why I made this folder, other than just “Oooh, looks cool.”. Even if it sounds kinda cringey, I made this folder for the future, for whoever reads this - be it my girlfriend of the time, my mum, or one of my other family members. If you are reading this, treat it like my personal thoughts on everything, and be prepared for a LOT of reading. I will attempt to make this be like my second brain, where all my notes, all my thoughts, everything, is kept, locally, for myself and whoever else I let read this.<br>Respectfully, if I’m still alive, and you’ve not been given permission to read through this, this is the last chance you have to keep my trust and respect.<br>Side note, in order of importance, I’d rank these folders as (for my thoughts):<br>
<br>Coding &amp; Software

<br>Why? This contains all of the projects I decided on making. From experience, someones code can show a lot about how they were feeling at that point.


<br>Daily

<br>Why? It’s quite literally a journal.


<br>Literature

<br>Why? I like books, I like poetry. It’s another way into how I’m thinking.


<br>School AND Japanese

<br>Why? These folders contain notes, some of which have my own personal thoughts mixed into them.


<br>Games

<br>Why? It’s the most direct. Most notes in here will be mainly facts from other websites, or, useless stuff. Look through here if you want, but, if you’re trying to get a look into my life, it’s not the first stop I’d recommend.


<br>Next page: <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="00 - Index/03 - To whoever reads this" data-href="00 - Index/03 - To whoever reads this" href="00-index/03-to-whoever-reads-this.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">03 - To whoever reads this</a>]]></description><link>00-index/02-why-i-made-this-folder.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Index/02 - Why I made this folder.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:09:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[03 - To whoever reads this]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Last page: <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="00 - Index/02 - Why I made this folder" data-href="00 - Index/02 - Why I made this folder" href="00-index/02-why-i-made-this-folder.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">02 - Why I made this folder</a><br>Once more, I welcome you to the guide to, what is in all form and function, my brain. If you’re reading this, then, I hope you find what you’re looking for. If you don’t, respectfully, leave my notes alone. I’m spending a lot of time of this, and as such, there’ll be multiple backups. If you’ve taken this drive, expecting to find something like porn or illegal stuff, you’ll be turning up a dead end (unless I turn into a degenerate). If you’ve taken this drive, hoping to sell it, do it. Just wipe everything off it first. I’ll still try to find my drive, however, I’ll at least have some sort of semblance of respect for you. As I said, I’ll back this drive up multiple times. Hell, I’m planning on buying 2 more 2TiB drives for whatever’s on here.]]></description><link>00-index/03-to-whoever-reads-this.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00 - Index/03 - To whoever reads this.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 01:14:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Japanese - Flashcards - Unit 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>はじめます（はじめる）:: To start<br>
おいたち :: personal history<br>
ようちえん :: kindergarten<br>
〜才の時 :: When I was ~ years old<br>
子どもの時 :: When I was a child<br>
七五三 :: festival for children of 3, 5 and 7<br>
にゅう学しき :: School entrance ceremony<br>
ランドセル :: school bag<br>
せい人しき :: coming of age ceremony<br>
はじめて :: first time<br>
さいごの日 :: last day<br>
くろい :: black<br>
かんたん（な）:: easy<br>
たいへん（な）:: hard<br>
しんせつ（な）:: kind<br>
おもい :: heavy<br>
ドラム :: drum<br>
わだいこ :: japanese drum<br>
アーチェリー :: archery<br>
きゅうどう :: Japanese archery<br>
スキー :: ski<br>
ネットバール :: netball<br>
コーチ :: coach<br>
チーム :: team<br>
ようふく :: clothes<br>
これ :: this<br>
また :: again]]></description><link>01-japanese/01-flashcards/japanese-flashcards-unit-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">01 - Japanese/01 - Flashcards/Japanese - Flashcards - Unit 1.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 06:50:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flashcards]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="01 - Japanese/01 - Flashcards/Japanese - Flashcards - Unit 1" data-href="01 - Japanese/01 - Flashcards/Japanese - Flashcards - Unit 1" href="01-japanese/01-flashcards/japanese-flashcards-unit-1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Japanese - Flashcards - Unit 1</a>]]></description><link>01-japanese/00-japanese-moc.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">01 - Japanese/00 - Japanese MOC.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 07:56:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aim]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>To create an assistant that has basic intelligence to recognise words and interpret them as different words. This will be used to help with daily tasks, such as adding events to calendars, tracking expenses, calculations, and other menial tasks. This can be easily added onto by creating python files in the modules/ folder, then adding the respective task onto a dictionary.<br><br>To prove it can be done.<br>Links:<br>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="02 - Coding &amp; Software/03 - Coding Languages/01 - Python/01 - Modules/Python - Custom Modules - Expenses" data-href="02 - Coding &amp; Software/03 - Coding Languages/01 - Python/01 - Modules/Python - Custom Modules - Expenses" href="02-coding-&amp;-software/03-coding-languages/01-python/01-modules/python-custom-modules-expenses.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Python - Custom Modules - Expenses</a>
<br>
]]></description><link>02-coding-&amp;-software/01-projects/python-dante.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">02 - Coding &amp; Software/01 - Projects/Python - DANTE.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What does this module aim to achieve?]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>This module aims to achieve three things at once:<br>
<br>Take input from user, and write the following to a document:

<br>Name of expense
<br>Cost of expense
<br>Category of expense


<br>Read the same document and print out past expenses
<br>Calculate affect on budget and print remaining
<br>Code:<br>]]></description><link>02-coding-&amp;-software/03-coding-languages/01-python/01-modules/python-custom-modules-expenses.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">02 - Coding &amp; Software/03 - Coding Languages/01 - Python/01 - Modules/Python - Custom Modules - Expenses.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Projects]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="02 - Coding &amp; Software/01 - Projects/Python - DANTE" data-href="02 - Coding &amp; Software/01 - Projects/Python - DANTE" href="02-coding-&amp;-software/01-projects/python-dante.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Python - DANTE</a><br><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="02 - Coding &amp; Software/03 - Coding Languages/01 - Python/01 - Modules/Python - Custom Modules - Expenses" data-href="02 - Coding &amp; Software/03 - Coding Languages/01 - Python/01 - Modules/Python - Custom Modules - Expenses" href="02-coding-&amp;-software/03-coding-languages/01-python/01-modules/python-custom-modules-expenses.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Python - Custom Modules - Expenses</a>]]></description><link>02-coding-&amp;-software/00-coding-moc.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">02 - Coding &amp; Software/00 - Coding MOC.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 07:57:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[School Subjects]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>]]></description><link>03-school/00-school-moc.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">03 - School/00 - School MOC.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 07:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DMC5 - Devil Breakers]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>04-games/01-devil-may-cry/01-devil-may-cry-5/dmc5-devil-breakers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">04 - Games/01 - Devil May Cry/01 - Devil May Cry 5/DMC5 - Devil Breakers.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 10:12:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nero]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>Nero can charge up his Red Queen sword as if it were a motorbike, increasing his attack power and speed of his attacks, which can also instantly charge one bar by pressing the charge button at the right time (or, if it’s at the perfect moment, fully charged). Every attack done uses 1 bar of the Exceed charge, excluding some, which use all of them. These excluded moves are:<br>
<br>EX Streak
<br>EX High Roller
<br>EX Payline
<br>EX Calibur
<br>EX Shuffle
<br><br>Nero has access to a wide variety of special toys, one that vibrates the fucking electro-magnetic field, and one of which... just vibrates. He can use these Breakers in a variety of ways, be it attacking, dodging, or, in the case of the vibrator, healing by jerking it off (actual line in the moves description). All of these Breakers have a reasoning behind why they’re called Devil Breakers. They break on one of 3 conditions - you get hit while in the middle of one of their moves, you use Breakage, or, you activate their special ultimate super deluxe move by holding down the style button until the Breaker glows. Nero can hold a max of 8 Breakers at any given time, and they’re scattered around (most) levels if needed. <br><br><br>After attempting to kill himself merge his human half with his demon half, Dante unlocks his SDT (NOT STD, VERY DIFFERENT THINGS). This is a form which, normally, is all or nothing - that is, you use the full bar, or don’t use the form. For Dante, it takes 12 bars of Devil Trigger to fully charge it up. During this state, Dante cannot use any other weapon than Devil Sword Dante, and the moveset is completely changed. The only way to extend the usage of this form to either buy the Trigger Heart ability, or to use the Quad S ability. The Quad S ability activates when you are at SSS Rank for style, and then going into SDT (hence, Quad S - SSS + SDT). It gives you a brief period where you can exit at no cost to the bar, but, if you do not exit during that time, it will return to normal. This is shown as a form of pure power, and brings Dante closer to Vergil’s beliefs - power is absolute.<br><br>Dante has access to 4 unique styles - <a data-href="#Trickster" href="about:blank#Trickster" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Trickster</a>, <a data-href="#Swordmaster" href="about:blank#Swordmaster" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Swordmaster</a>, <a data-href="#Gunslinger" href="about:blank#Gunslinger" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Gunslinger</a> and <a data-href="#Royalguard" href="about:blank#Royalguard" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Royalguard</a>. I go over them briefly in his <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Nero / Dante" data-href="#Nero / Dante" href="about:blank#Nero_/_Dante" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Devil Trigger</a> section, however, this section is more dedicated to them. When you’re not in DT and/or don’t have DSD’s floating swords around you, these effects are weaker and more limited - except for Royalguard, where the swords don’t directly enhance the effect. I will go over each effect in their own chapter.<br><br>The easiest to learn of the four styles, this style allows for faster movement - and provides invincibility frames during use. The style can be used both mid-air and on the ground, and is somewhat reminiscent of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Vergil (character)" data-href="#Vergil (character)" href="about:blank#Vergil_(character)" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vergil</a>’s dodge move, as is with a lot of their moves. Dante is able to dash to any direction he wants, however, once he dashes once in mid-air, he begins descending, which can be reset by jumping on an enemy (as with Air Hike), and is also able to teleport to the enemy (slightly in air with basic input) by locking on and holding forward while using the style button. This teleport can be enhanced by doing Back-&gt;Forward + Style instead of just holding forward, placing you on the ground instead of in air. While Devil Sword Dante’s swords float around you, Trickster is enhanced for faster dodges and for more air dashes (2-3 extra) or air teleports.<br><br>Swordmaster is a slightly more complicated style to learn, however, is still quite easy. In all situations, it provides the user with more moves to use - be it air attacks for Rebellion or DSS, extra combos for Cavaliere, or access to the Fire Moveset for King Cerberus. A majority of these moves are for combo extenders (Rebellion/DSS), combo finishers (King Cerberus), or just hard hitting moves (Cavaliere), however, can also be Jump-Cancelled out of to extend these further, as with almost any move. With DSD, you’re able to use the spectral swords on it, giving access to imitations of multiple moves, and the only move DSD kept from DSS and Rebellion in Swordmaster - Dance Macabre. When you have DSD’s spectral swords floating around you from Swords Formation, or Devil Trigger while DSD is equipped, the swords will follow and attack alongside your attacks, with DSD being the most accurate with these hits.<br><br>Gunslinger is probably one of my favourite styles, after Swordmaster. It is also the BEST combo extender style that Dante has. With Dual Kalina Ann, Dante can relaunch enemies, with Dr Faust, Dante can deal even more than he already does with the weapon (without even attacking), with Shotgun, you get a second pair of nunchucks to use (but with bullets). Other than just being a great combo extender, Gunslinger also makes weapons that might not be too good pretty damn decent and/or fun to use (see: Shotgun, where it combines Trickster with the gun shots). With DSD’s swords, they shoot at anything that is a threat (such as Vergi’s Summon Swords in his Boss Fight), knocking small enemies over, and dealing a decent amount of damage.<br><br>The “git gud, schum” style. If you hit it right, you block all damage at no cost. If you hold the button/tap too early, you block all damage at the cost of DT. If you use Lock-On + Back + STYLE and hold it, you block all damage and hit the enemy back (very useful for Furries, I mean Furies). With DSD’s swords, Royalguard will ALWAYS block some damage, even if you’re fucking stupid and don’t even tap the button. It, uh, doesn’t help for Hell and Hell, but it does work.<br><br><br>The concentration meter, Vergil’s only unique mechanic (with SDT being a shared mechanic of Dante), and one that does a surprising amount for something that is barely talked about. With Yamato, the attacks reach further, with Mirage Edge, the attacks hit more often, and with Beowulf, almost every attack can be charged to a third stage. Concentration is also a requirement for all Super Moves - technically excluding World of V, but for it to actually do something, you need Level 1 Concentration. Every weapon has it’s own Super Move (Yamato technically having two!), all related to one of it’s abilities. Yamato has Judgement Cut End - a VASTLY upgraded form of Judgement Cut, dealing similar damage at every range of the attack - and, World of V, if you count Vergil stabbing himself with the Yamato as being a Yamato Super Move - which heals the user on use, for varying amounts depending on Concentration level, and dealing damage (but not killing anything till the end), generating more Green Orbs for any killed enemy, during which, Vergil is also immune to all damage. Mirage Edge has Deep Stinger, pretty much Dante’s SDT Stinger move, but much stronger, not much more I can add on to that. Finally, Beowulf has Hell on Earth, the user puts their fucking spirit into one punch, charges it up (by looks of it, to Level 3 due to the purple glow at the peak), then smashes the ground. It deals most damage at close range, and almost nothing at long range.<br><br>Vergil’s Sin Devil Trigger, on the surface, acts very similarly to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Sin Devil Trigger" data-href="#Sin Devil Trigger" href="about:blank#Sin_Devil_Trigger" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dante’s</a>, requiring the bar to be charged to the max to be used. However, it is when you enter the form that changes are noticeably drastic. Unlike Dante, Vergil has access to all 3 of his weapons, and their original movesets - albeit, with moves added on, and with quite a few moves/combos slightly altered. It also enhances his speed, and his roll is changed to a dash to the side/dash to the back, both moves that can be done outside of the form, albeit with more inputs (Triangle + Lock-On + L Stick to the side + X / Lock-On + Back-&gt;Foward + Circle). All 3 of his weapons gain a Super Move, similar to Dante’s Judgement in his SDT. However, unlike Dante’s Judgement, Vergil is able to use these moves in his human form (downside being that the full SDT bar is used and not just a quarter).<br><br><br><br>Nero and Dante share the same version of a DT, you activate it, you change forms, and you become more powerful. In the case of Nero, his Buster moves (IN SOME CASES) become stronger, and he gains spinning spectral swords whenever he shoots his gun - reminiscent of Vergil’s summon swords. Dante, however, uses his DT for his Styles, and for certain moves. When he uses Stinger (DSD, DSS or Rebellion), he loses a bar or two of DT, and the same is true for Redline, however, the moves gain a LOT of power in return. When using each style, Dante also gains certain buffs when DSD is equipped - Trickster gives him faster dashes, and 4 in the air instead of 1, due to the 4 spectral swords floating behind him; Gunslinger shoots the spectral swords at “Threats”, such as enemies, or, in the case of the Vergil boss battle, Vergil’s summoned swords; Swordmaster has the swords attack alongside whatever attack Dante is doing at the time, being much more accurate to the sword when DSD is being used, where they merge back into the sword; and, finally, Royalguard has them used as a shield to limit damage if you fail to guard, or you just fail a guard.<br><br>V uses his Devil Trigger as a way to control the beast called Nightmare, or, as a way to allow his summons to attack on their own - practically just Auto Mode without the debuff, even the devs didn’t like playing him. While Nightmare is out, his white hair shows, and his summons are immortal (or revived if killed). V can also directly control Nightmare by hopping on his back, slowing the DT drain, however, treating the DT as Nightmare’s health bar (as what Shadow and Griffon have). Other than that, there’s not really anything with V’s DT - he gains no health regen from it, however, he does get more green orbs in general. <br><br>Vergil’s DT is one of the more interesting situations. Due to his beliefs for absolute power, a popular theory is that he changed his normal DT to his new Doppleganger after unlocking his Sin Devil Trigger - going all out from the start, instead of slowly increasing his power like Dante, or perhaps Nero, would do, to toy with their enemy. His Doppleganger is always locked to the Yamato, allowing for some interesting combos if you know what you’re doing, and can’t replicate Judgement Cut End. If Vergil goes into SDT, the Doppleganger’s moveset will change to match the form change. The Doppleganger also has 3 speeds - default, slow, and fast. These speeds affect the rate at which DT will be used as well - slow uses it slowly, fast uses it faster, and default uses it at the normal rate. No matter what speed you choose, any Perfect Judgement Cut will come out at the same speed as Vergil, with the teleport also being at the same time. ]]></description><link>04-games/01-devil-may-cry/01-devil-may-cry-5/dmc5-mechanics.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">04 - Games/01 - Devil May Cry/01 - Devil May Cry 5/DMC5 - Mechanics.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 10:11:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Devil May Cry 5]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="04 - Games/01 - Devil May Cry/01 - Devil May Cry 5/DMC5 - Mechanics" data-href="04 - Games/01 - Devil May Cry/01 - Devil May Cry 5/DMC5 - Mechanics" href="04-games/01-devil-may-cry/01-devil-may-cry-5/dmc5-mechanics.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">DMC5 - Mechanics</a><br>
<a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="04 - Games/01 - Devil May Cry/01 - Devil May Cry 5/DMC5 - Devil Breakers" data-href="04 - Games/01 - Devil May Cry/01 - Devil May Cry 5/DMC5 - Devil Breakers" href="04-games/01-devil-may-cry/01-devil-may-cry-5/dmc5-devil-breakers.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">DMC5 - Devil Breakers</a>]]></description><link>04-games/00-games-moc.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">04 - Games/00 - Games MOC.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 07:58:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Books]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>]]></description><link>05-literature/00-literature-moc.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">05 - Literature/00 - Literature MOC.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 07:58:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DAILY NOTE]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br>Customize this template to your liking!<br>
...<br><br><br><br><br>
<br>DAILY TASKS:

<br>Daily Missions
<br>PvP Flowers
<br>Co-Op
<br>Free Summons (if applicable)
<br>Tournament of Power
<br>Store Free Item


<br>Work on any current event
]]></description><link>99-meta/00-templates/(template)-daily.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">99 - Meta/00 - Templates/(TEMPLATE) Daily.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DAILY NOTE]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>...<br><br>
<br>Task 1
<br>Task 2
<br>Task 3
]]></description><link>99-meta/00-templates/(template)-daily-(vanilla).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">99 - Meta/00 - Templates/(TEMPLATE) Daily (Vanilla).md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 01:06:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[(TEMPLATE) Unique]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>99-meta/00-templates/(template)-unique.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">99 - Meta/00 - Templates/(TEMPLATE) Unique.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 01:06:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[202401211512 Notebook CSS Classes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
This page is only for keeping CSS classes ready for autocomplete.
]]></description><link>99-meta/preloaded-classes/202401211512-notebook-css-classes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">99 - Meta/Preloaded Classes/202401211512 Notebook CSS Classes.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 01:06:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[202403091325 General Tweaks CSS Classes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
This page is only for keeping CSS classes ready for autocomplete.
]]></description><link>99-meta/preloaded-classes/202403091325-general-tweaks-css-classes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">99 - Meta/Preloaded Classes/202403091325 General Tweaks CSS Classes.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 01:06:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Obsidian]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>A website version of my brain. Updated whenever I feel like it.<br><br>Hello, whoever is reading this. I hope you enjoy the website, or the raw code if you're into that stuff (wouldn't blame you). I've ommitted all my Daily notes from here, as to protect the privacy of both me and my friends. Respectfully, do not take any code you find in here. If you do, I'll... give you a very stern rant.<br><br>Why what? Why upload all of my notes detailing my school work, assignments, etc? I can. Plus, it's a backup. If, for some godforsaken reason, someone steals my laptop, PC, 2tib harddrive, all of my USBs, deletes my Google Account and my phone(s), well, I'm not able to access my notes, but at least I have a backup (good luck stealing all of that, though, I hide stuff pretty well if I say so myself). If they delete my GitHub account on top of all of this, I am screwed (unless I've given a copy of this to others).<br><br>Me, myself, and anyone else. It's my thoughts, my life, hell, you can even just say it's who I am. The projects I work on, the notes I take, every word I type, it all links back to who I am. By reading this, I hope you get a better understanding of who I am, because, honestly, I barely have an understanding of who I am in this world.<br><br>As I stated before, I've ridded this vault of all mentions of my friends names (as to protect their privacy), and removed my Daily Notes, to protect mine. I hope you enjoy wandering through this ever-growing garden of my thoughts (I'm not done with porting all my notes over, give it a week, and it should be like triple the size).<br><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="00 - Index/00 - MAIN PAGE" data-href="00 - Index/00 - MAIN PAGE" href="00-index/00-main-page.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">00 - MAIN PAGE</a>]]></description><link>readme.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">README.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 07:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>